brainbell.com 2019-05-04

# Privacy Policy - : BrainBell

BrainBell respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. That is why we have adopted this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy lets you know how your personal information is processed and used. We promise that we will take steps to use your personal information only in ways that are compatible with this Privacy Policy. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

## Information Collection and Use

BrainBell collects personal information when you register with BrainBell. This is optional and for registration purposes only. Registration allows you to participate in the BrainBell activities and allows us to identify you as a unique member of the BrainBell.

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the BrainBell service, such as service announcements and administrative messages, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.

We do not collect personal information when you visit our site **unless you signup for a service** , place an order, register, complete a survey or enter a contest. When you signup for a service, we will ask you for the following personal information: name and e-mail address. We may use your personal information to contact you for account purposes. When you place an order, we will ask you for the following personal information: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, and credit card number and its expiration date. This information is requested to verify your identity. This information is transmitted via a secure encrypted server using **Secure Sockets Layer** (SSL) technology, the approved industry standard. We may use your personal information to contact you for account purposes. When you submit feedback or questions via e-mail, or contact us for information about our Web site, we will request your name and e-mail address. We use this information solely to respond to your inquiries.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

BrainBell certifies that all personal information relating to its members and clients, including email addresses and personal information, will be kept confidential. We do not share, sell, rent or barter any identifiable personal information to any third party.

## Cookies and Web Beacons

From time to time, BrainBell or its advertisers may send a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your Internet browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can't read data off of your computer hard disk or read cookie files created by other Web sites. Cookies do not damage your system. We use cookies to identify which areas of BrainBell's you have visited or customized, so the next time you visit, those pages may be readily accessible. Our advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) may also use cookies and web beacons to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. Our advertisers may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your Internet browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our Site and other Web sites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

By using the BrainBell, you consent to the collection and use of information by BrainBell as specified above. We reserve the right to modify this policy. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

## Questions and Suggestions

If you have questions or comments about BrainBell's privacy policy, please feel free to contact us : info@brainbell.com.

by updated Aug 01, 2016
